Gagan Gogna

+1 (91) 8054950420:: <u>GAGANGOGNA08@GMAIL.COM</u>

Summary

Accomplished Assistant Manager with in-depth experience consistently rising through ranks. Well-versed in sales, personnel management and inventory management. Dedicated to complete knowledge of company products and services for optimized customer service.

Skills

- Organizational Skills
- Training and Development
- Communication Skill
- Selection and Recruitment
- Staff Management
- Helth & Saftey
 Management
- Project Management
- Customer Service

Certificate

 Holder of License Controller Qualification and Manager Certificate (NZQA)

Work history

Assistant Manager (Nector Foods)

Ludhiana - October 2020 - Current

- Generated repeat business through exceptional customer service and responded to customer concerns with friendly and knowledgeable service.
- Reviewed sales and gross profit reports to assess company efficiency.
- Helped with planning schedules and delegating assignments to meet coverage and service demands.
- Completed regular inventory counts to verify stock levels, address discrepancies, and forecast future needs.

Duty Manager LIQUORLAND TE RAPA

Hamilton - November 2015 - March 2018

- Trained new employees on day-to-day operations of the business
- Managed vendor claims and delivery issues,
 Monitored and evaluated cost-effectiveness and efficiency of store operations.
- Bridge management and employee relations by addressing demands, grievances or other issues
- Assisted in the development of marketing materials and campaigns to use for promotions and advertising.
- Created successful work schedules for each team member to maintain deadlines and fully staffed shifts.
- Inspected stocks to identify shortages, replenish supply and maintain consistent inventory.

Education

• Bachelor of Arts: PANJAB UNIVERSITY, CHANDIGARH (2011 – 2014)

 GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN Human Resource Management

WAIKATO INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (WINTEC) Hamilton, New Zealand (2015-2016)